Guide to the Albert R. Mann papers, 1916-1931.
Mann, Albert R. papers, 1916-1931.
- Cornell University Related Materials, 1917-1931
  - Business Office (December 1919), 1919-12 (Box 11, Folder 61)
  - Business Office (January 1920), 1920-01 (Box 11, Folder 62)
  - Business Office (January 1920), 1920-01 (Box 11, Folder 63)
  - Business Office (January 1920), 1920-01 (Box 11, Folder 64)
  - Business Office (January 1920), 1920-01 (Box 11, Folder 65)
  - Business Office (February 1920), 1920-02 (Box 11, Folder 66)
  - Business Office (February 1920), 1920-02 (Box 11, Folder 67)
  - Business Office (March 1920), 1920-03 (Box 11, Folder 68)
  - Business Office (March 1920), 1920-03 (Box 11, Folder 69)
  - Business Office (March 1920), 1920-03 (Box 11, Folder 70)
  - Business Office (April 1920), 1920-04 (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Business Office (April 1920), 1920-04 (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - Business Office (April 1920), 1920-04 (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - Business Office (May 1920), 1920-05 (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - Business Office (May 1920), 1920-05 (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - Business Office (May 1920), 1920-05 (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - Business Office (June 1920), 1920-06 (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - Business Office (June 1920), 1920-06 (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - Chemistry - M. C. Burritt, 1919-1920 (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - Civil Engineering, 1919-1920 (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - Commencement committee, 1919-1920 (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - Publications Committee, 1919-1920 (Box 12, Folder 12)
    Johannsen, O. A.
  - Publications Committee, 1919-1920 (Box 12, Folder 13)
  - Committee on University Policy, 1919-1920 (Box 12, Folder 14)
  - Comptroller (University), 1919-1920 (Box 12, Folder 15)
  - Cornell Countryman, 1919-1920 (Box 12, Folder 16)
  - Council (Agricultural College), 1919-1920 (Box 12, Folder 17)
  - Curtis, C. E., 1919-1920 (Box 12, Folder 18)
  - Curtis, C. E., 1919-1920 (Box 12, Folder 19)
  - Curtis, C. E., 1919-1920 (Box 12, Folder 20)
  - Curtis, C. E., 1919-1920 (Box 12, Folder 21)
  - Curtis, C. E., 1919-1920 (Box 12, Folder 22)
  - 1919 Dairy Industry, 1919-1920 (Box 12, Folder 23)
  - 1919 Dairy Industry, 1919-1920 (Box 12, Folder 24)
  - 1920 W. A. Stocking, 1919-1920 (Box 12, Folder 25)
  - 1920 W. A. Stocking, 1919-1920 (Box 12, Folder 26)
  - Educational Policy, 1919-1920 (Box 12, Folder 27)
  - Entomology, 1919-1920 (Box 12, Folder 28)
    Herrick, G. W.
    Comstock, A. B.
    Crosby, C. R.
  - Entomology, 1919-1920 (Box 12, Folder 29)
  - Entomology, 1919-1920 (Box 12, Folder 30)
  - Entomology, 1919-1920 (Box 12, Folder 31)
  - Extension Teaching (July-August), 1919-1920 (Box 12, Folder 32)
  - Extension Teaching (July-August), 1919-1920 (Box 12, Folder 33)
  - Extension Teaching (September-December), 1919-1920 (Box 12, Folder 34)
  - Extension Teaching (January-April), 1919-1920 (Box 12, Folder 35)
  - Extension Teaching (January-April), 1919-1920 (Box 12, Folder 36)
  - Extension Teaching (May-June), 1919-1920 (Box 12, Folder 37)
  - Extension Teaching (May-June), 1919-1920 (Box 12, Folder 38)
  - Faculty (College), 1919-1920 (Box 12, Folder 39)
  - Faculty (University), 1919-1920 (Box 12, Folder 40)
  - Farms, 1919-1920 (Box 12, Folder 41)
  - Farm Bureaus, 1919-1920 (Box 12, Folder 42)
  - Farm Bureaus, 1919-1920 (Box 12, Folder 43)
  - Farm Bureaus, 1919-1920 (Box 12, Folder 44)
  - Farm Crops, 1919-1920 (Box 12, Folder 45)
    Montgomery, E. R.
    Thompson, H. C.
  - Farm Crops, 1919-1920 (Box 12, Folder 46)
  - Farm Crops, 1919-1920 (Box 12, Folder 47)
  - Farm Crops (January-March 1920), 1920-01-1920-03 (Box 12, Folder 48)
  - Farm Crops (January-March 1920), 1920-01-1920-03 (Box 12, Folder 49)
  - Farm Crops (April-June 1920), 1920-04-1920-06 (Box 12, Folder 50)
  - Farm Crops (April-June 1920), 1920-04-1920-06 (Box 12, Folder 51)
  - Farm Crops (April-June 1920), 1920-04-1920-06 (Box 12, Folder 52)
  - Farm Management, 1919-1920 (Box 12, Folder 53)
  - Farm Management, 1919-1920 (Box 12, Folder 54)
  - Farm Management, 1919-1920 (Box 12, Folder 55)
  - Farm Management, 1919-1920 (Box 12, Folder 56)
  - Farm Practice, 1919-1920 (Box 12, Folder 57)
    King, A. C.
  - Farm Practice, 1919-1920 (Box 12, Folder 58)
  - Floriculture, 1919-1920 (Box 12, Folder 59)
  - Floriculture, 1919-1920 (Box 12, Folder 60)
  - Forestry, 1919-1920 (Box 12, Folder 61)
    Hosmer, R. S.
  - Forestry, 1919-1920 (Box 12, Folder 62)
  - Forestry, 1919-1920 (Box 12, Folder 63)
  - Heads of Departments, 1919-1920 (Box 12, Folder 64)
  - Heads of Departments (January-March 1920), 1920-01-1920-03 (Box 12, Folder 65)
  - Heads of Departments (January-March 1920), 1920-01-1920-03 (Box 12, Folder 66)
  - Heads of Departments (March-June 1920), 1920-03-1920-06 (Box 12, Folder 67)
  - Heads of Departments (March-June 1920), 1920-03-1920-06 (Box 12, Folder 68)
  - Heads of Departments (March-June 1920), 1920-03-1920-06 (Box 12, Folder 69)
  - Home Economics, 1919-1920 (Box 12, Folder 70)
  - Home Economics, 1919-1920 (Box 12, Folder 71)
  - Home Economics, 1919-1920 (Box 12, Folder 72)
  - Home Economics, 1919-1920 (Box 12, Folder 73)
  - Home Economics, 1919-1920 (Box 12, Folder 74)
  - Home Economics, 1919-1920 (Box 12, Folder 75)
  - Home Economics, 1919-1920 (Box 12, Folder 76)
  - Home Economics, 1919-1920 (Box 12, Folder 77)
  - Home Economics, 1919-1920 (Box 12, Folder 78)
  - Home Economics, 1919-1920 (Box 12, Folder 79)
  - Home Economics, 1919-1920 (Box 12, Folder 80)
  - Home Economics, 1919-1920 (Box 12, Folder 81)
  - Home Economics, 1919-1920 (Box 12, Folder 82)
  - Home Economics, 1919-1920 (Box 12, Folder 83)
  - Home Economics, 1919-1920 (Box 12, Folder 84)
  - Information Service, 1919-1920 (Box 12, Folder 85)
  - Information Service, 1919-1920 (Box 12, Folder 86)
  - Information Service, 1919-1920 (Box 12, Folder 87)
  - Information Service, 1919-1920 (Box 12, Folder 88)
  - Information Service, 1919-1920 (Box 12, Folder 89)
  - Information Service, 1919-1920 (Box 12, Folder 90)
  - Information Service, 1919-1920 (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Information Service, 1919-1920 (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - Printed Matter (Information Service), 1919-1920 (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Landscape Art, 1919-1920 (Box 13, Folder 4)
    Curtis, Ralph W.
    Gorton Davis, E.
  - Landscape Art, 1919-1920 (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - Law College, 1919-1920 (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - Library (College), 1919-1920 (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - Medical College, 1919-1920 (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - Meteorology, 1919-1920 (Box 13, Folder 9)
    Wilson, Wilford M.
    Mordoff, R. A.
  - Music Department, 1919-1920 (Box 13, Folder 10)
    Dann, Hollis E.
  - Plant Breeding, 1919-1920 (Box 13, Folder 11)
    Love, H. H.
  - Plant Breeding, 1919-1920 (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - Plant Breeding, 1919-1920 (Box 13, Folder 13)
  - Plant Breeding, 1919-1920 (Box 13, Folder 14)
  - Plant Breeding, 1919-1920 (Box 13, Folder 15)
  - Plant Breeding, 1919-1920 (Box 13, Folder 16)
  - Plant Pathology, 1919-1920 (Box 13, Folder 17)
    Barrus, M. F.
  - Plant Pathology, 1919-1920 (Box 13, Folder 18)
  - Plant Pathology, 1919-1920 (Box 13, Folder 19)
  - Plant Pathology, 1919-1920 (Box 13, Folder 20)
  - Plant Pathology, 1919-1920 (Box 13, Folder 21)
  - Plant Pathology, 1919-1920 (Box 13, Folder 22)
  - Plant Pathology, 1919-1920 (Box 13, Folder 23)
  - Plant Pathology, 1919-1920 (Box 13, Folder 24)
  - Pomology, 1919-1920 (Box 13, Folder 25)
  - Pomology, 1919-1920 (Box 13, Folder 26)
  - Poultry Husbandry, 1919-1920 (Box 13, Folder 27)
  - Poultry Husbandry, 1919-1920 (Box 13, Folder 28)
  - Poultry Husbandry, 1919-1920 (Box 13, Folder 29)
  - Poultry Husbandry, 1919-1920 (Box 13, Folder 30)
  - Poultry Husbandry, 1919-1920 (Box 13, Folder 31)
  - Poultry Husbandry, 1919-1920 (Box 13, Folder 32)
  - Poultry Husbandry, 1919-1920 (Box 13, Folder 33)
  - Reading Course for the Farm, 1919-1920 (Box 13, Folder 34)
  - Registrar - University, 1919-1920 (Box 13, Folder 35)
  - Rural Economy, 1919-1920 (Box 13, Folder 36)
  - Rural Economy, 1919-1920 (Box 13, Folder 37)
  - Rural Education, 1919-1920 (Box 13, Folder 38)
    Works, G. A.
  - Rural Education, 1919-1920 (Box 13, Folder 39)
  - Rural Education, 1919-1920 (Box 13, Folder 40)
  - Rural Education, 1919-1920 (Box 13, Folder 41)
  - Rural Education, 1919-1920 (Box 13, Folder 42)
  - Rural Education, 1919-1920 (Box 13, Folder 43)
  - Rural Education, 1919-1920 (Box 13, Folder 44)
  - Rural Engineering, 1919-1920 (Box 13, Folder 45)
    Riley, H. W.
  - Rural Engineering, 1919-1920 (Box 13, Folder 46)
  - Rural Organization, 1919-1920 (Box 13, Folder 47)
  - Rural Organization, 1919-1920 (Box 13, Folder 48)
  - Rural Organization, 1919-1920 (Box 13, Folder 49)
  - Shurman, J. G., President, 1919-1920 (Box 13, Folder 50)
  - Shurman, J. G., President, 1919-1920 (Box 13, Folder 51)
  - Shurman, J. G., President, 1919-1920 (Box 13, Folder 52)
  - Shurman, J. G., President, 1919-1920 (Box 13, Folder 53)
  - Shurman, J. G., President, 1919-1920 (Box 13, Folder 54)
  - Secretary, College, 1919-1920 (Box 13, Folder 55)
  - Secretary, College, 1919-1920 (Box 13, Folder 56)
  - Secretary, College, 1919-1920 (Box 13, Folder 57)
  - Secretary, College, 1919-1920 (Box 13, Folder 58)
  - Secretary, College, 1919-1920 (Box 13, Folder 59)
  - Secretary, University, 1919-1920 (Box 13, Folder 60)
  - Secretary, University, 1919-1920 (Box 13, Folder 61)
  - Sibley College, 1919-1920 (Box 13, Folder 62)
    Smith, A. W.
  - Soils, 1919-1920 (Box 13, Folder 63)
  - Soils, 1919-1920 (Box 13, Folder 64)
  - Soils, 1919-1920 (Box 13, Folder 65)
  - Soils, 1919-1920 (Box 13, Folder 66)
  - Summer School, 1919-1920 (Box 13, Folder 67)
  - Treasurer's Office, 1919-1920 (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - Treasurer's Office, 1919-1920 (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - Treasurer's Office, 1919-1920 (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - Treasurer's Office, 1919-1920 (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - Treasurer's Office, 1919-1920 (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - Treasurer's Office, 1919-1920 (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - Treasurer's Office, 1919-1920 (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - University Christian Association, 1919-1920 (Box 14, Folder 8)
    Edwards, R. H.
  - University Christian Association, 1919-1920 (Box 14, Folder 9)
  - Veterinary College, 1919-1920 (Box 14, Folder 10)
  - Zoology, 1919-1920 (Box 14, Folder 11)
  - Agricultural Experiment Station, 1919-1920 (Box 14, Folder 12)
    Jordan, W. H.
  - Agricultural Experiment Station, 1919-1920 (Box 14, Folder 13)
  - Agricultural Experiment Station, 1919-1920 (Box 14, Folder 14)
  - Allen, E. W. (Chief, Office of Experiment Station), 1919-1920 (Box 14, Folder 15)
  - Allen, E. W. (Chief, Office of Experiment Station), 1919-1920 (Box 14, Folder 16)
  - Architect (State), 1919-1920 (Box 14, Folder 17)
  - Attorney General (State), 1919-1920 (Box 14, Folder 18)
  - Comptroller (State), 1919-1920 (Box 14, Folder 19)
  - Department of Agriculture (State), 1919-1920 (Box 14, Folder 20)
  - Department of Agriculture (State), 1919-1920 (Box 14, Folder 21)
  - Department of Agriculture (State), 1919-1920 (Box 14, Folder 22)
  - Department of Agriculture (Washington), 1919-1920 (Box 14, Folder 23)
  - Department of Agriculture (Washington), 1919-1920 (Box 14, Folder 24)
  - Department of Agriculture (Washington), 1919-1920 (Box 14, Folder 25)
  - Department of Agriculture (Washington), 1919-1920 (Box 14, Folder 26)
  - Department of Education (State), 1919-1920 (Box 14, Folder 27)
  - Department of Education (State), 1919-1920 (Box 14, Folder 28)
  - Department of Education (State), 1919-1920 (Box 14, Folder 29)
  - Income Funds, 1919-1920 (Box 14, Folder 30)
  - Income Funds, 1919-1920 (Box 14, Folder 31)
  - Income Funds, 1919-1920 (Box 14, Folder 32)
  - Secretary of Agriculture (Washington), 1919-1920 (Box 14, Folder 33)
  - Smith, Alfred E. (Governor), 1919-1920 (Box 14, Folder 34)
  - Smith, Alfred E. (Governor), 1919-1920 (Box 14, Folder 35)
  - State Agricultural Society, 1919-1920 (Box 14, Folder 36)
  - States Relations Service (General), 1919-1920 (Box 14, Folder 37)
    Benson, O. H.
  - States Relations Service (General), 1919-1920 (Box 14, Folder 38)
    Smith, C. B.
  - States Relations Service (General), 1919-1920 (Box 14, Folder 39)
    True, A. C.
    Lloyd, W. A.
  - States Relations Service (General), 1919-1920 (Box 14, Folder 40)
  - Wilson, Charles S. (Commissions), 1919-1920 (Box 14, Folder 41)
  - Miscellaneous Matters, 1920-1921 (Box 16, Folder 18)
  - Vice-Dean and Vice-Directors, 1920-1921 (Box 16, Folder 19)
  - Abstracts, 1920-1921 (Box 16, Folder 20)
  - Animal Husbandry, 1920-1921 (Box 16, Folder 21)
    Harper, M. W.
  - Animal Husbandry, 1920-1921 (Box 16, Folder 22)
  - Animal Husbandry, 1920-1921 (Box 16, Folder 23)
  - Animal Husbandry, 1920-1921 (Box 16, Folder 24)
  - Animal Husbandry, 1920-1921 (Box 16, Folder 25)
  - Animal Husbandry, 1920-1921 (Box 16, Folder 26)
  - Animal Husbandry, 1920-1921 (Box 16, Folder 27)
  - Architecture, 1920-1921 (Box 16, Folder 28)
  - Arts and Sciences, 1920-1921 (Box 16, Folder 29)
  - Arts and Sciences, 1920-1921 (Box 16, Folder 30)
  - Attorney (University), 1920-1921 (Box 16, Folder 31)
  - Botany, 1920-1921 (Box 16, Folder 32)
  - Botany, 1920-1921 (Box 16, Folder 33)
  - Botany, 1920-1921 (Box 16, Folder 34)
  - Buildings and Grounds, 1920-1921 (Box 16, Folder 35)
  - Buildings and Grounds, 1920-1921 (Box 16, Folder 36)
  - Buildings and Grounds, 1920-1921 (Box 16, Folder 37)
  - Buildings and Grounds, 1920-1921 (Box 16, Folder 38)
  - Burrit, M. C., 1920-1921 (Box 16, Folder 39)
  - Burrit, M. C., 1920-1921 (Box 16, Folder 40)
  - Burrit, M. C., 1920-1921 (Box 16, Folder 41)
  - Burrit, M. C., 1920-1921 (Box 16, Folder 42)
  - Burrit, M. C., 1920-1921 (Box 16, Folder 43)
  - Burrit, M. C., 1920-1921 (Box 16, Folder 44)
  - Burrit, M. C., 1920-1921 (Box 16, Folder 45)
  - Burrit, M. C., 1920-1921 (Box 16, Folder 46)
  - Burrit, M. C., 1920-1921 (Box 16, Folder 47)
  - Burrit, M. C., 1920-1921 (Box 16, Folder 48)
  - Burrit, M. C., 1920-1921 (Box 16, Folder 49)
  - Burrit, M. C., 1920-1921 (Box 16, Folder 50)
  - Burrit, M. C., 1920-1921 (Box 16, Folder 51)
  - Burrit, M. C., 1920-1921 (Box 16, Folder 52)
  - Burrit, M. C., 1920-1921 (Box 16, Folder 53)
  - Burrit, M. C., 1920-1921 (Box 16, Folder 54)
  - Business Office, 1920-1921 (Box 16, Folder 55)
  - Business Office, 1920-1921 (Box 16, Folder 56)
  - Business Office, 1920-1921 (Box 16, Folder 57)
  - Business Office, 1920-1921 (Box 16, Folder 58)
  - Business Office, 1920-1921 (Box 16, Folder 59)
  - Chemistry, 1920-1921 (Box 16, Folder 60)
  - Chemistry, 1920-1921 (Box 16, Folder 61)
  - Civil Engineering, 1920-1921 (Box 16, Folder 62)
  - Library Committee, 1920-1921 (Box 16, Folder 63)
  - Publications Committee, 1920-1921 (Box 16, Folder 64)
  - Publications Committee, 1920-1921 (Box 16, Folder 65)
  - Comptroller (University), 1920-1921 (Box 16, Folder 66)
  - Comptroller (University), 1920-1921 (Box 16, Folder 67)
  - Comptroller (University), 1920-1921 (Box 16, Folder 68)
  - Comptroller (University), 1920-1921 (Box 16, Folder 69)
  - Comptroller (University), 1920-1921 (Box 16, Folder 70)
  - Comptroller (University), 1920-1921 (Box 16, Folder 71)
  - Comptroller (University), 1920-1921 (Box 16, Folder 72)
  - Cornell Countryman, 1920-1921 (Box 16, Folder 73)
  - Council, Agricultural College, 1920-1921 (Box 16, Folder 74)
  - Council, Agricultural College, 1920-1921 (Box 16, Folder 75)
  - Council, Agricultural College, 1920-1921 (Box 16, Folder 76)
  - Council, Agricultural College, 1920-1921 (Box 16, Folder 77)
  - Dairy Industry, 1920-1921 (Box 16, Folder 78)
  - Dairy Industry, 1920-1921 (Box 16, Folder 79)
  - Dairy Industry, 1920-1921 (Box 16, Folder 80)
  - Dairy Industry, 1920-1921 (Box 16, Folder 81)
  - Dairy Industry, 1920-1921 (Box 16, Folder 82)
  - Dairy Industry, 1920-1921 (Box 16, Folder 83)
  - Dairy Industry, 1920-1921 (Box 16, Folder 84)
  - Entomology, 1920-1921 (Box 16, Folder 85)
  - Entomology, 1920-1921 (Box 16, Folder 86)
  - Entomology, 1920-1921 (Box 16, Folder 87)
  - Entomology, 1920-1921 (Box 16, Folder 88)
  - Entomology, 1920-1921 (Box 16, Folder 89)
  - Extension Teaching, 1920-1921 (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - Extension Teaching, 1920-1921 (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - Extension Teaching, 1920-1921 (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - Extension Teaching, 1920-1921 (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - Extension Teaching, 1920-1921 (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - Extension Teaching, 1920-1921 (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - Extension Teaching, 1920-1921 (Box 17, Folder 7)
  - Extension Teaching, 1920-1921 (Box 17, Folder 8)
  - Extension Teaching, 1920-1921 (Box 17, Folder 9)
  - Extension Teaching, 1920-1921 (Box 17, Folder 10)
  - Extension Teaching, 1920-1921 (Box 17, Folder 11)
  - Faculty (College), 1920-1921 (Box 17, Folder 12)
  - Faculty (University), 1920-1921 (Box 17, Folder 13)
  - Farm Bureaus, 1920-1921 (Box 17, Folder 14)
  - Farm Bureaus, 1920-1921 (Box 17, Folder 15)
  - Farm Crops, 1920-1921 (Box 17, Folder 16)
  - Farm Crops, 1920-1921 (Box 17, Folder 17)
  - Farm Crops, 1920-1921 (Box 17, Folder 18)
  - Farm Crops, 1920-1921 (Box 17, Folder 19)
  - Farm Crops, 1920-1921 (Box 17, Folder 20)
  - Farm Crops, 1920-1921 (Box 17, Folder 21)
  - Farm Crops, 1920-1921 (Box 17, Folder 22)
  - Farm Management, 1920-1921 (Box 17, Folder 23)
  - Farm Management, 1920-1921 (Box 17, Folder 24)
  - Farm Management, 1920-1921 (Box 17, Folder 25)
  - Farm Management, 1920-1921 (Box 17, Folder 26)
  - Farm Management, 1920-1921 (Box 17, Folder 27)
  - Farm Management, 1920-1921 (Box 17, Folder 28)
  - Farm Practice, 1920-1921 (Box 17, Folder 29)
  - Farm Practice, 1920-1921 (Box 17, Folder 30)
  - Farm Practice, 1920-1921 (Box 17, Folder 31)
  - Farm Practice, 1920-1921 (Box 17, Folder 32)
  - Farms Rent, 1920-1921 (Box 17, Folder 33)
  - Floriculture, 1920-1921 (Box 17, Folder 34)
  - Floriculture, 1920-1921 (Box 17, Folder 35)
  - Forestry, 1920-1921 (Box 17, Folder 36)
  - Forestry, 1920-1921 (Box 17, Folder 37)
  - Forestry, 1920-1921 (Box 17, Folder 38)
  - Graduate School, 1920-1921 (Box 17, Folder 39)
  - Heads of Departments and Circular Letters, 1920-1921 (Box 17, Folder 40)
  - Heads of Departments and Circular Letters, 1920-1921 (Box 17, Folder 41)
  - Heads of Departments and Circular Letters, 1920-1921 (Box 17, Folder 42)
  - Heads of Departments and Circular Letters, 1920-1921 (Box 17, Folder 43)
  - Home Economics, 1920-1921 (Box 17, Folder 44)
  - Home Economics, 1920-1921 (Box 17, Folder 45)
  - Home Economics, 1920-1921 (Box 17, Folder 46)
  - Home Economics, 1920-1921 (Box 17, Folder 47)
  - Home Economics, 1920-1921 (Box 17, Folder 48)
  - Home Economics, 1920-1921 (Box 17, Folder 49)
  - Home Economics, 1920-1921 (Box 17, Folder 50)
  - Home Economics, 1920-1921 (Box 17, Folder 51)
  - Home Economics, 1920-1921 (Box 17, Folder 52)
  - Home Economics, 1920-1921 (Box 17, Folder 53)
  - Home Economics, 1920-1921 (Box 17, Folder 54)
  - Home Economics, 1920-1921 (Box 17, Folder 55)
  - Home Economics, 1920-1921 (Box 17, Folder 56)
  - Home Economics, 1920-1921 (Box 17, Folder 57)
  - Home Economics, 1920-1921 (Box 17, Folder 58)
  - Home Economics, 1920-1921 (Box 17, Folder 59)
  - Home Economics, 1920-1921 (Box 17, Folder 60)
  - Home Economics, 1920-1921 (Box 17, Folder 61)
  - Home Economics, 1920-1921 (Box 17, Folder 62)
  - Home Economics, 1920-1921 (Box 17, Folder 63)
  - Honor System, 1920-1921 (Box 17, Folder 64)
  - Curtis, C. E., 1920-1921 (Box 17, Folder 65)
  - Curtis, C. E., 1920-1921 (Box 17, Folder 66)
  - Curtis, C. E., 1920-1921 (Box 17, Folder 67)
  - Curtis, C. E., 1920-1921 (Box 17, Folder 68)
  - Information Service, 1920-1921 (Box 17, Folder 69)
  - Information Service, 1920-1921 (Box 17, Folder 70)
  - Information Service, 1920-1921 (Box 17, Folder 71)
  - Information Service, 1920-1921 (Box 17, Folder 72)
  - Information Service, 1920-1921 (Box 17, Folder 73)
  - Junior Extension Notes, 1920-1921 (Box 17, Folder 74)
  - Junior Extension Notes, 1920-1921 (Box 17, Folder 75)
  - Junior Extension Notes, 1920-1921 (Box 17, Folder 76)
  - Landscape Art, 1920-1921 (Box 17, Folder 77)
  - Law College, 1920-1921 (Box 17, Folder 78)
  - Library (College), 1920-1921 (Box 17, Folder 79)
  - Library (University), 1920-1921 (Box 17, Folder 80)
  - Mechanical Engineering, 1920-1921 (Box 17, Folder 81)
  - Medical College, 1920-1921 (Box 17, Folder 82)
  - Meteorology, 1920-1921 (Box 17, Folder 83)
  - Music Department, 1920-1921 (Box 17, Folder 84)
    Dann, H. E.
  - Plant Breeding, 1920-1921 (Box 17, Folder 85)
  - Plant Breeding, 1920-1921 (Box 17, Folder 86)
  - Plant Breeding, 1920-1921 (Box 17, Folder 87)
  - Plant Breeding, 1920-1921 (Box 17, Folder 88)
  - Plant Breeding, 1920-1921 (Box 17, Folder 89)
  - Plant Breeding, 1920-1921 (Box 17, Folder 90)
  - Plant Breeding, 1920-1921 (Box 17, Folder 91)
  - Plant Pathology, 1920-1921 (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - Plant Pathology, 1920-1921 (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - Plant Pathology, 1920-1921 (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - Plant Pathology, 1920-1921 (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - Plant Pathology, 1920-1921 (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - Pomology, 1920-1921 (Box 18, Folder 6)
    Heinicke, A. J.
  - Pomology, 1920-1921 (Box 18, Folder 7)
  - Chandler, W. H., 1920-1921 (Box 18, Folder 8)
  - Chandler, W. H., 1920-1921 (Box 18, Folder 9)
  - Chandler, W. H., 1920-1921 (Box 18, Folder 10)
  - Chandler, W. H., 1920-1921 (Box 18, Folder 11)
  - Chandler, W. H., 1920-1921 (Box 18, Folder 12)
  - Poultry, 1920-1921 (Box 18, Folder 13)
    Rice, J. E.
  - Poultry, 1920-1921 (Box 18, Folder 14)
  - Poultry, 1920-1921 (Box 18, Folder 15)
  - Poultry, 1920-1921 (Box 18, Folder 16)
  - Poultry, 1920-1921 (Box 18, Folder 17)
  - Poultry, 1920-1921 (Box 18, Folder 18)
  - Poultry, 1920-1921 (Box 18, Folder 19)
  - President's Office, 1920-1921 (Box 18, Folder 20)
  - President's Office, 1920-1921 (Box 18, Folder 21)
  - President's Office, 1920-1921 (Box 18, Folder 22)
  - President's Office, 1920-1921 (Box 18, Folder 23)
  - Rea, George H., 1920-1921 (Box 18, Folder 24)
  - Rea, George H., 1920-1921 (Box 18, Folder 25)
  - Rea, George H., 1920-1921 (Box 18, Folder 26)
  - Registrar (University), 1920-1921 (Box 18, Folder 27)
  - Rural Education, 1920-1921 (Box 18, Folder 28)
    Wright, W. J.
  - Rural Education, 1920-1921 (Box 18, Folder 29)
  - Rural Education, 1920-1921 (Box 18, Folder 30)
  - Rural Education, 1920-1921 (Box 18, Folder 31)
  - Rural Education, 1920-1921 (Box 18, Folder 32)
  - Rural Education, 1920-1921 (Box 18, Folder 33)
  - Rural Education, 1920-1921 (Box 18, Folder 34)
  - Rural Engineering, 1920-1921 (Box 18, Folder 35)
  - Rural Engineering, 1920-1921 (Box 18, Folder 36)
  - Rural Organization, 1920-1921 (Box 18, Folder 37)
  - Rural Organization, 1920-1921 (Box 18, Folder 38)
  - Rural Organization, 1920-1921 (Box 18, Folder 39)
  - Semi-Centennial Endowment, 1920-1921 (Box 18, Folder 40)
  - Semi-Centennial Endowment, 1920-1921 (Box 18, Folder 41)
  - Semi-Centennial Endowment, 1920-1921 (Box 18, Folder 42)
  - Secretary (College), 1920-1921 (Box 18, Folder 43)
  - Betten, Cornelius, 1920-1921 (Box 18, Folder 44)
  - Betten, Cornelius, 1920-1921 (Box 18, Folder 45)
  - Betten, Cornelius, 1920-1921 (Box 18, Folder 46)
  - Betten, Cornelius, 1920-1921 (Box 18, Folder 47)
  - Betten, Cornelius, 1920-1921 (Box 18, Folder 48)
  - Betten, Cornelius, 1920-1921 (Box 18, Folder 49)
  - Betten, Cornelius, 1920-1921 (Box 18, Folder 50)
  - Secretary (University), 1920-1921 (Box 18, Folder 51)
  - Secretary (University), 1920-1921 (Box 18, Folder 52)
  - Smith, Hughes v. -Lever Correspondence, 1920-1921 (Box 18, Folder 53)
  - Smith, Hughes v. -Lever Correspondence, 1920-1921 (Box 18, Folder 54)
  - Smith, Hughes v. -Lever Correspondence, 1920-1921 (Box 18, Folder 55)
  - Smith, Hughes v. -Lever Correspondence, 1920-1921 (Box 18, Folder 56)
  - Smith, Hughes v. -Lever Correspondence, 1920-1921 (Box 18, Folder 57)